Guide to the Arboretum at Connecticut College Records, 1890-2016 (inclusive), 1930-1990 (bulk) RG51
Linda Lear Center for Special Collections and Archives
- Series VIII: Richard Goodwin's historical research of the Arboretum, 1890-1999
  - Hurricane 1938, crca 1938 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Institutionalizing the land re: land use, circa 1965-1990 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Land records notes and annotated maps, circa 1973-1991 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Maps and forms, circa 1948-1988 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Maps and forms, circa 1948-1988 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Maps and forms, circa 1948-1988 (Box 0S2, Folder 1)
  - Maps and forms, circa 1948-1988 (Box 0S2, Folder 2)
  - New London Historical newspaper, May 6, 1946 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - News clippings, 1934-1990 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Notes and checklists, 1982, undated (Box 22, Folder 0)
  - Outlines and notes, undated (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Personal research and Arboretum reports, 1973-1995 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Proprietor's records, undated (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Research on deeds: Blunt House (640 Williams Street), Coast Guard Academy, and Connecticut College, undated (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - "The Rogerenes" address at "All Souls' Church, 1980 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Rogers Cemetery; includes drafts of presentations, 1996 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Rogers family; includes genealogical research, undated (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Rogers Mamacoke farm, undated (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Slosberg Rainbow estates, 1995 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Solider's Lot, undated (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Stonebridge subdivision; includes information on Pralevis property, 1996-1997 (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - Taylor gift, tract 31, 1992 (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - Thames improvement campaign, undated (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - Thames River, Smith's Cove (4 East of Turnpike), undated (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - Tract A: State Wildlife Sanctuary publicity, 1955-1959 (Box 22, Folder data_value_missing_1b6e0fd8c8999f1aed92277ce6511af1)
  - Waterford, undated (Box 22, Folder data_value_missing_612c90acbe7d1881344f444e5fd73c40)
  - "What Happened at Quaker Hill," Thames Science Center National Quarterly, 1975 (Box 22, Folder data_value_missing_c98616b3ecb7a8a510abe49493293755)
  - Woodworth, Grace Calvert, undated (Box 22, Folder data_value_missing_6531b2d2b355a54451ae5b97d80a127b)